rcg.org 2019-04-07

# Privacy Policy

Your privacy on the Internet is a fundamental element of our websites. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it among our Internet assets.

#### What Information We Collect

The Restored Church of God ( _rcg.org_ ) and its related assets ( _worldtocome.org_ and _realtruth.org_ ) actively collect and analyze data about their users. For instance: User demographics, search engine referrals, subjects of interests, and news and services most useful.

Users who sign up to one of our email subscription lists are required to supply some or all of the following formation: (1) name, (2) email address, (3) country and (4) ZIP/postal code. Additional optional fields or related questions may also be asked. All information allows us to determine accurate demographics and improve the services we provide.

#### How We Collect Information

There are various ways in which we are permitted to obtain information about you through the following processes:

 **Email Subscription and Forms:** Users may register for one of our email mailing lists or request literature from our websites. These inform users of various updates and changes to our websites or are to facilitate the efficient processing of literature requests.

 **Cookies:** A _cookie_ is a small data file that websites write to your hard drive when you visit them. It most often contains information such as a user ID that sites use to customize information presentation or track the visited pages. We use this information to optimize our site navigation, design and performance. You are always free to decline our “cookies” if your browser permits, but this may limit some aspects of website functionality.

 **IP Addresses:** We collect IP address information for the purposes of system administration, to report aggregate (collective) information, and to audit the use of our services and materials. Because we automatically collect and store statistics about your online activities on an aggregated basis, this information is not always personally identifiable. We do not link IP addresses to personal identification, unless given prior approval or to necessarily troubleshoot a problem.

#### How We Use and Disclose Your Information

_Rcg.org_ , _worldtocome.org_ and _realtruth.org_ use any user information voluntarily given by users to enhance their website experience, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the sites or to better prepare future content based on the interests of users.

In some cases, we use your personally identifiable information to provide information to you, such as, but not limited to, newsletters and email offers.

We will not make any information that we collect from users available to the general public in any form without the prior written consent of the effected user unless: (a) the information is already publicly available, or (b) such disclosure is required by law, court order, or is requested by other government or law enforcement authority.

#### Security

The Restored Church of God (and related assets) utilizes industry-standard security procedures to protect all personally identifiable information within its control from loss, misuse or unauthorized alteration. Such security protocols include firewalls, encryption, password protection and physical on-site security.

DESPITE THESE SECURITY MEASURES, WE CANNOT GUARANTEE THAT ALL OF YOUR PRIVATE COMMUNICATIONS OR PERSONAL INFORMATION WILL NEVER BE DISCLOSED OR UNLAWFULLY ACCESSED BY UNAUTHORIZED THIRD PARTIES.

#### Opt-out Policy

A user may remove himself from our email subscriptions at any time. We will send a confirmation message of the intent to remove data to the current email address registered for that user. The user must respond to that confirmation message within three (3) business days. Upon reply, your information is completely removed from our database. If a confirmation message is not received, we will continue to maintain the registrant and related data.

#### Limits on Our Abilities

While your privacy is very important to us, due to the existing legal and regulatory environment, we cannot fully ensure that your private communications and other personally identifiable information will not be disclosed to third parties. For example, we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. Additionally, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to private entities, such as law enforcement or other government officials, as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to investigate or resolve possible problems or inquiries.

#### Copyright and Trademark Policy

This site is the primary and official source of web-based information about The Restored Church of God. Recognizing that there are people who wish to promote our efforts on the Internet by maintaining web pages that parallel this website, we have adopted the following policy to ensure consistency and protect against error.

All of the content and graphics contained in this website are copyrighted 2000-2019 and owned by The Restored Church of God. Certain items are also protected as a trademark or a registered trademark of The Restored Church of God. The Restored Church of God maintains and reserves exclusive rights to the license and use of the same.

We ask that any and all content and graphics that reference or relate to The Restored Church of God or this website be submitted to us for review and approval before being displayed on the Internet.

#### User Complaints

User complaints regarding our privacy practices should be sent to Website Services.
